Right and million years and million years. I would never bother anybody that's a bother me
I would never like harm me to these channel. I'd never ever
A million years when I'm whom I'd like bother anybody anyway. I never complain about wages. I would never
Matters I would never
Let's say horrible things about people
Thank you, Vicky
I'm perfect. No, who's perfect? I'd ever heard anybody know a million years. I would not have a fly
You don't want to harm a fly?
One of our hockey it's we're dancing in the mystery my positive
That's all of them. Pog is gonna like me once that you're you're laughing at
refusing from me
Hand of my liquor. I would think I'd some water
Will send me so they want to me something go ahead
You can see just what you knew I put water in the sun drink the water
How about you like you send me like some some water?
Try and let me
Everyone's been acting weird in life anymore.
Everyone's bad at me.
Too late, I'm not his boss.
Yes, he's that, honey.
You're not the boss of me now.
All right, so.
I'm sorry guys look I didn't take a shower. I just like I brush my teeth and my nails. They were clean
I mean my nails my tutorial nails are you like that way? You know not perfect
And you're not so big
You're the boss me
Up to everyone. I think I won't do it. It's good. So well
We but it's nice
What is this? What is this?
I wonder if you remember that.
That.
Those are like, I've seen it before.
These are wasted. Wasted shakes.
I have one more.
I have a couple of energy drinks that you have.
It's 11.0. Oh my gosh.
So early.
Was my friend we get to this together guys. I don't know we have in this together now
We have to hang out. I don't know everyone's mad
10 people like 10 people in this street
It's harsh
No one's to hang out anymore like normally no one's even membership. Oh, well, I suppose I hang out
Last dance panel
What is this? Are you mad at me? Are you mad at me? Let's go. Let's go. What's wrong? You guys are mad at me?
What I don't want to crash out. What does it mean? I don't know what it means. I don't know what it means.
I'm gonna crash out.
Vicky, you're good.
Lay down the hammer.
down little fella. Oh, my god.
Hey man, what's going on? What
you in for? I don't know. Well,
because guys, why are you going
to remind me? I don't know.
There's okay. Oh, yeah, because
God started talking about it
Yeah, I like I like God. Oh, yeah. Oh my god. I just yeah, you should have a good job, brother
That was a good. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I know
I mean, it's like God is like so sneaky he knows better at this point
He knows he knows better even say that word. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh my god
No, he's just trying so yeah got was it a slip up or he just fucking do it
Hey, guys, let me see the first slip up.
Good end.
I don't know
that word starts with a G, great. It's not that word, but it's different, you know what I'm saying,
like you can get around YouTube. No, I know, I know, I mean, it's just so easy, I mean, it's like,
it's just like, you know, changing a syllable or like a letter of work. It was a good day and I'm not
going to be psyche on this one. Yeah, I'm going to be good. Yeah.
Okay, it was good to end it. I just don't like, I don't want to hear, he was like, he was like saying it and he was like so happy like, oh he's like, oh yeah.
It's your channel, brother. It's your channel, dude.
Well, Kati, why are you doing that?
You gotta take initiative.
I love it. I don't think he's watching.
I don't think he's watching. He's not here.
Oh, I don't think Kati's here. Kati's not here.
I mean, you did nothing wrong.
That's not sure there were so many people talking at once. I was laughing at are you here to me? I was laughing at
We're not right tonight, but there's
They had to pay for you. Are you saying that some other time that somebody called you something horrible?
I don't know. You don't have to do that. Where did I defend you?
Because I'm pretty good at defending you because I did it on so much, you know. I'm pretty good at defending you on a good channel.
You defended me, Gus? Yeah. You did? Oh, yeah, of course, yeah, I asked him where. Yes, I did.
Chris, Chris, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. What's up, Chris?
Chris, I'm really sorry. I'm sorry.
I don't know why he thinks happening to where you got in the stream and restarted every time, like, nobody's doing anything crazy.
He said the, he told me that somebody said the R word, and I don't mean dumb dumb, I mean the other R word, like SA word.
Don't say it, but the SA word.
Oh, okay. Say word where you take advantage of a woman. Yeah
Yeah, that's me for me to say that on YouTube dude. What the fuck?
I don't I don't but I just I feel like
People are trying to say things and then strikes when they say when they say things so
Chris he's just trying to look out for his fucking channel, but you can't say that word though
It breaks you like yeah, like fucking go. You need a like I said make a rumble dude
Try it out and you can see a rumble that would be
You're fucking so that would be good cuz like you probably love it on fucking rumble
Dude, he is so fucking paranoid all the time on YouTube where he's got it like look how many times like I've been here like fucking like two hours
He's really used to have it like he's the least a lot like yeah, but it's YouTube brother. We can't help that though
It's not his fault. It's YouTube's fault. It's not his fault though. He's trying to protect his channel
Yeah, I get it. Come on Chris. You know you know that. Yeah. I know man. It's just like fuck
You're not arguing with Psyche though. You're arguing with YouTube. You're not arguing with him. You're gonna with YouTube
It's TOS. It's not Psyche. He's just following YouTube
Now you're making the argument
Mine is now argument you're making another argument that maybe he's going like rumble or something, but he's not on there
Which would be a good idea, but he's not on there. He's trying to protect his ass. You can't make an argument. That's that like you'd protect your fucking ass
You'd protect your job, wouldn't you?
Yeah, well, I mean fucking here's the you can um, you can fucking the stream that
Multi-stream on rumble and fucking tell your fucking audience to go to that
You could do that. Yes, you could but he doesn't though brother. He's just trying to protect his channel
I feel listen. I feel bad for him because I know he's like stressed out when he streams
He's like stressed out the whole time like that's not fine. Yeah, especially with all the shit
He does with being like a low
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it's
We work stress somebody that is doing just purely for fun. It's not even yeah
Could you say the wrong thing that you know what you're jumping it? You know what you're jumping to you?
Yeah, it's gonna be a way. Yeah, it's on this monitor. So you understand that it's on this monetize
It's gonna take differently than somebody that is not worried about monetization they
Are you gonna get monetized?
When they're breaking TOS you're never gonna get monetized. I mean look at like my games one of the biggest fucking craters out there
He's got demonetized because when he's passed out before he's left me on here fucking like and I stand for like hours
And you see how bad it was
No, I could easily like it was on his channel. I was on it was only me and I was talking to like this. Yeah
Didn't you just say they were calling him like the G word when they say in the F word
Which I I don't mean fuck, but they were saying F word
They were seeing all kinds of shit when you were up here, right?
Yeah, bad things they were porn bombing Chris you literally just made the argument like literally like 45 minutes ago
Like that's literally what you said. I do like you're up here alone
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so don't disrespect the man for protecting his channel, you know, which I don't think you're doing Chris, but
I'm saying I'm in general. I'm talking to other people. I'm not talking to you Chris at all
Don't disrespect the man for like defending his channel. I feel bad for him, too. And I argue this all the time
Hey, put your put your foot down. This is this is my channel. This is how it's gonna go if you don't like it then you can go
Then but you like your way tonight. She'll everyone in then we then you have to like
Try to kick people out but then when it gets to you've set to end it
But you know what you do psyche almost all the time you start another channel again right after that
Start that shit again
My channel is fine. My channel is absolutely fine. My channel is just like absolutely fine.
Okay, see you in my next one. Guys, hold on. I just want to do something real quick, guys.
I love you guys. Let me see.
Yeah.
This is just, this is-
No, but it's like-
I love-
Yeah, you guys, you guys-
Dude!
Guys, it's like-
You're like, God, I will stand up.
It's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it can mask me on this. I would love that.
But if someone wants to like, you know, just like, go.
I just want to say I don't love people better.
The more content it is, the more viewers he gets.
So fuck it, but you know what I'm saying?
He knows it, obviously.
That's true until Chris, here's my argument,
until they break TOS.
So yeah, the more controversial they are, great.
You get more views, but until they break TOS.
So you got to vet people out like God, Wolfman.
The door even destiny I would actually I didn't actually have her back up before I'd have somebody like
This random people like showing some dick or something like that's crazy
Okay, summer summer summer. You got a members summer. You got a membership. I love that summer was the first membership
It's not appropriate. Oh
Maybe a KT received a membership
I'm gonna see out there. I'll be right there. 25 bucks.
Scotty, Scotty D. Yeah, that was 25 bucks worth there.
Yeah, but if anyone wants to like donate a membership,
it could be, you know, yeah, Vicky, yeah.
You know, just know that I appreciate everything.
We've had a lot of memberships.
I started donating five memberships just to show you guys.
Yeah, congratulations to members.
I'm sorry if you can get a membership,
but you know, I think people that did deserve one.
Pretty much, you know, I think everyone deserves it though, but hey guys, there's some other ships
Yep. Yeah, free ones if you're as well
Like yeah, I wasn't trying to debate you or nothing. I was
No, you're fine. I don't want to you know what people accuse me like like you're trying to run the show
No, I'm just trying to look out for my my my boy
If I was trying to look out for my friend like people would never say that but you know the internet and shit, so
I know I know
I'm always I'm always about that like unless I'm debating like yeah, but I'm I always look out for your channel
You have to admit that it's been like months and months and months now. Don't break to us. Like it's not your channel
I know it's not my channel, but don't break to us. Don't I always try to look out for you, but you know, whatever
It's it's it's a I can't you know, I can't imagine like fucking uh, I mean
I'm not like what's been like two hours and he's restarted this stream like what?
Four times. I'm so sorry. I mean you have to take some accountability
I should fault stop letting people up here that you don't fucking know unless you're gonna vent out
And I'm not trying to get hard with you at all brother. I'm just gonna be a little
You know, I'm not I always look out for you. Do I not?
You know for streaming on YouTube like it's rough to try to like progress cuz like fucking I mean there's there's people that make videos
They get they get fucking more, you know, I don't know it's it
My god
We do want to like take out if you knew what I had the possibility of being gifted membership
You know the click the five games up there and say I opt in for the membership and then you can be
Eligible I've gotten like probably like over 25 members says
What if every members of the channel
YouTubers have gotten a gotten you know, I've talked about this before you know like Roman outwood for instance
He has his own clothing line Spalmark. I don't know if you're gonna hit
He got a fucking copyright or like fucking whatever strike because of like clothing. He wore on his on his strings
drinks he had in his fucking kitchen
like would you would you start making videos and fucking on shit like that you know he has to like take the
Water bottle labels off. I mean, this is real dude. I'm not lying, bro. Like fucking so like you know me. Yeah
Yeah
Okay, yeah, I didn't do the five memberships. I think people don't do the memberships. I think you guys
You can do it man like Roman like that fool did it man. He's fucking he's milliner
well
If I were they can figure out how to make a million dollars. I was I could do it
Maybe he put you right back. He got strikes for fucking wearing like a Nike shirt
Right and he said fuck you YouTube
I'm gonna make my own clothing line
With my own shit that way I could wear that all all day long and fucking you can't say shit and he did it and look now
Look every VOD this guy puts up. It's got a million views. That's like that's like fucking a thousand dollars per video type shit
Motherfuckers a million rolling out with
Yeah, yeah, I remember cuz he has like this he has this like saltwater fish tank
I would love a saltwater fish tank
And you can you can fuck in a
If you like leave your house and go on vacation you can like you know
There's like you get on your app and you can like feed your fish
It's pretty dope. I want to get up and you get like you get like fucking uh
Like core core coil coral
that grows and shit you could like you could like fix your take up and like you know saltwater tanks are hard to maintain
But if you if you go through this certain
These certain people, I mean, I know it's like another state, but I'm sure they have it everywhere
But they actually watch it watch before you
You gotta pay money money money money money
You get that so Chris so Chris so Chris have a I'm sure reading for you a few cars
Yeah, somewhere like your member you see your members summer. I was sure reading for you
Yeah, I'm fucking
Are you doing your cards? I believe you cards do what I pull you a few cards
Yeah, me pull my shirt. Let's go. Okay. Yeah, of course
We'll shuffle more shuffle better
Shut up right here
so
What are you thinking about?
What do you think about something with love or you think what's like you're like?
That was love right here. It's me with love. I see
Wait, well tell me what you see
What are you thinking about?
like
Money like money
You want some money? Okay?
Money, okay?
First she gets the money then he gets the power then he gets the women, right? Okay?
Okay
We're gonna come together with somebody. Okay. You're running. You come together with somebody. What is this?
It's cherry. I'm moving forward. She says, okay
Straight. Okay. You got some power there. Okay
Okay, more than advice. Okay
Yes, okay
Well, no, there's this one chick that I've tried to like uh talk to like recently like like lately lately
Yeah, let's take your time to talk to you. Well, I see they yeah, you're wanting to come together with somebody
There's like the two of hedgehogs. I'm trying to see turn me down because I tried to get her Instagram and shit
And she's like, uh, she's like, I don't remember what it is
I don't have an Instagram or whatever and I was like, okay
She's like next time or whatever. I'm like, okay, cuz I go to this area they go this place a lot
well not a lot but like, you know, what's it all and
You know I wear like you know slipknot shirts and fucking tools. She's like I thought she's like tools my favorite band
I'm like oh really?
I'm like fuck a I'm like let me get your Instagram like fucking can I hit you up like you go to fucking show
I'm like you go to shows in fucking Vegas like I want to fucking come with me
Yeah
Her
Or somebody else
Alison's right there, and I think that it is powerful like you know force they make story right so it's like it's kind of like
Overpowering our afterwards. I was like she might be fucking that one has a boyfriend or even married and like fucking that's probably like why
You know, I mean that could be the force. That's part of what it was
Well, we have what you have the
AT of swords, which is like you you're mentally you're mentally stuck in your head about this the seven of hedgehogs
Let me see seven of hedgehogs seven is also the chair. You have the chair earlier
I say you move forward with your plans, you know, there might be like some kind of like
Especially the idea you have among all the other ideas. Yeah, look at your club is where you met
Yeah, give me some kind of special ideas a little bit different than the others
There you go with that idea because there you have a lot of ideas
What that is what that is everybody else coming to tell me fucking how to live my life all these other people and I'm fucking
I'll listen to their fucking opinions. I'll listen what they say, but I'm gonna do what I want at the end of the day
Yeah, I hope I didn't like come across and try to tell you what to do
Okay
Good. It's my link kid. Oh my links not even 10 guys. Oh my gosh
Everybody thinks they know what's best for me, dude
Listen, I fucking last time I fucking listen. You're a fucking your advice. I got fucked over and I should have fucking
I should have not listened. I should have done what I was gonna do the first place like fuck you
Do that, you know your advice all sure you're glad tell me
Okay, you know, I mean, but at the end of the day, I'm gonna use my fucking brain
I'm gonna do my my choice my life texture and that's that's it. So fuck you
Not you, but you know what I mean, like, you know what I mean?
Me?
Well, you, he says it's me.
No, not you.
Not you.
Not you, bro.
No, not me.
Not me.
OK.
All these people in my life that I have, like my fucking brother,
like I was doing fucking, they fucking know what's best for me.
Like, I know what's best for me, dude.
Like, you're not in my fucking head.
You're not in my life.
You know what I mean?
So that's it.
Right.
And I'm always like that.
I'm always like that, bro.
So fucking, you know, that's it.
There you go, guys.
OK.
It's OK, Chris.
It's it's it's it's it's it's
Right Bob. It's kind of like right up the street. It's it's called a flex. I went there and I live streamed it
I mean I'll do some more streams. Listen. I fucking well. I don't have time
You're interested to be at a gay bar, but you know you get to travel over here pick me up after the gay bar
You know buy me several drinks and we do last year
Perfect. I mean I'm down to come to what where you live redot redondo, right? Yeah
Guys
Yes, well, no, I got a fucking thing because I had you know, I have to fucking figure it out
Okay, we'll see what we'll talk about it later. Okay, just think about certain just start thinking about it now
but no we're like the chat's talking about what you know, I went to this bar and
You know, I brought I brought Samson the same guy that I brought back to my pad this black this black this, you know
the African-American guy
Wait, was it him? No
What no
And I'd like they'd let me live stream. I sat the fucking live stream on the goddamn bar
I sat there and this fucking all these fucking, you know
You know gave guys came up to me and kept like hitting on me. You want to drink and all this? I'm like sure
You know in his number all this shit. I'm like, hey, I'm not what what what what happened with Samson
What happened with Samson YouTube? I brought him back here. I mean it was like a homeless guy and
You know really like he was like a gentle giant. I brought him back here and
I gave some beer or whatever he was tired. He like fell asleep on my couch for like a couple hours
I was still screaming
and
Go he insured over your boundaries
No, I
Get I could feel people dude when I when I talked to him
I know I knew he wasn't gonna fucking threaten me or try to like fucking like murder me or whatever like whatever people think
I
Got I got vibes on shit. You know me
Okay, and he was he was a good guy, but he just I don't know. Yeah, I think it was like mentally
Yeah, you know challenge or whatever, but like, you know, he was he was cool dude like uh
You know this is you know everybody's you know, that's what I'm saying
Is that what I got to do? You know me to get fucking views on my fucking shit
but like the game I
Fucking a IRL stream
So so we remember with the trans and would you be with the trans or you can see it would you ever consider it? I
mean
Unless it was like, you know, I didn't know about it. I mean, I'm not, I mean, I'm not trying to like do that, you know
It's a pretty damn it
Not for you that means because I mean there is like, I mean, you know, I mean you chat you guys know like I've
Accidentally seen pictures. I'm like, oh, that's that chick is hot as fuck. Wait a minute. She's a guy
You know, I mean, so that's where I'm at. I'm like, whoa. Oh shit
I
Nothing, you know have nothing against that. I'm just trying to like I
Mean I can't I can be a woman that I can be a woman all the time
You could have been all fooled. I
woman
I think I'm a guy
Imagine that when I was a woman Chris K if I was really a woman, would you take me?
I mean, somebody do a AI version of fucking this guy fucking as a chick, I shouldn't tell you.
Okay, I don't know. I don't know. I should just stop.
No, I'm just fucking his dick, bro.
If I chill with you and we went out on, you know, went to some bars or whatever, I mean, you being fucking gay would probably like get more chicks off the ground.
Honest then did I you know me cuz you know me? Yeah chicks chicks
Yeah, I don't know if I'm attracted. I mean all the chicks are here in my chat
These fools in chat dude fucking busters bro, what I see all cool as you summer Katrina
You know
Jonathan
me as Slayer, Jamie's Cowboys is here. Yeah, it's not cool people. What do you have at
Buster's? Is it Buster's? These bulls fucking, they don't fucking, they don't stream, they
just come on here and fucking because they're fucking, you know, here's the thing, listen.
summer's a shiver
where everyone go, I don't know, maybe Bita's streaming? I'm not sure
Yeah, Bita's a good page, I want to actually try to fucking get a hold of her later
if I shit like she did
Yeah, oh yeah, Bita's in the room
I just don't know if I remember shit
Can you remember? Are you a coherent to remember?
Tell me
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Okay. Yeah, I don't think it's very bad. Well, it was a page doing it. Okay, Justin
Well, she's probably got up, you know, she probably didn't get on the internet
We're spunky as summer's a merchant's turn shot summer. I'll do it summer doing a mod. I'll mod you too
You remember
Justin yeah
Okay, okay, are you all yours distract me through some some other stream that's talking about
Tell me. Oh, yeah, there's summer shadow. Thank you so much
Guys if you're here, I'm gonna post your job. Hey. Hey, so so uh, so
Uh, okay, you're on rumble
You want yeah some of the asses
You should make one bro
Just make one check it out and then you could maybe fall back on it if you get in trouble on youtube
You could always like tell your fucking audience and they go over there. I would that's what I would say
Or even multi-stream multi-stream just fucking when you go live on youtube you can fucking there's a program
You can when you hit live, it'll fucking OBS. You got OBS. I mean, I don't know what to use
I
You psyche retarded
You took everyone's wrench and gave them all back within a week. You didn't even last a week you moron
You're not learning
Summer should not have a wrench Christine. You're so stupid and everybody sees it. You're the biggest dickhead up here
I'm taking everyone's wrench. Here you go. Everyone has it back
I only want three mods. I'm sticking to five. Count your mods. You got like 30 again. You fucking retarded asshole.
You're not gonna learn motherfucker.
Give it all back. Give everybody the wrench back.
Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. Oh, no
Today all sites got to do is go into his YouTube settings and go to the moderated settings
He can see every you know who who's all banned he can unbanned and whoever he wants
If they go rogue
Those go rock rogue mods and fucking, you know, you're gonna be unmodded like fucking, you know me
Just tell your mods what what you want done and fucking if they don't listen then fucking unmod them. It's as easy as that
Just cuz the mods don't like specific fucking people, you know, and they're in their fucking opinion don't use you, you know
I don't know guys. It's those pages guys, but please those pages through. I don't know as page page wildflowers. I
Don't know and pay it up. I'm sorry for out page wildflowers guys those page. It's okay. It's okay
Just a but that was your reading. I think you get I think I'll forget you get reading cause I'm mad at me
YouTube is hard, dude. I gotta give I gotta fucking up psych fucking props as a fuck to try to fucking like
maintain
Then the this type of fucking play, you know what you're constantly streaming with fucking all these people that hate you
Because that's what it is motherfuckers that come on here to fucking porn bomb and shit like they're jealous and they're fucking
Trying to like fucking bring him down who hates him who hates you psych?
Hey, everybody give me a name. Give me one fucking name. Who hates you dude?
That's what I'm saying, right? Is it Boyle is it Justin Boyle who hates you?
I don't want to tell you that I don't want you to I don't I don't want the person you heard
Like I won't hurt them too bad
I'll give him a little skin cancer. I'll give him a little skin cancer that, you know, I really, somebody else can tell you, but I'm not going to say anything.
Yeah, I'm sure he fucking knows. There's specific people out there that fucking are trying to sabotage his success that he's trying to fucking acquire.
But you know what? God is like a powerful force.
It's crazy. It's crazy.
Right like I'm always watching all the time every time he streams. He's like, oh shit. Yeah, leave the bud like fucking
Well, Chris, give me a name Chris. Give me a name
One fucking name one name. I don't really
Just make one up that I mean, I mean they feel like the
I don't know. He's he's been restarting his string like I've been here like maybe three hours or two hours maybe
Like four times he like ended it and I'm like I noticed I'm like it says ended and I'm stuck in the
Streamyard with like people
He ended the stream after ten minutes one night, what do you talk about two hours like four times
I don't know what he thought that was gonna get him in trouble, but he like in it like what was it?
What was it? I mean, that's real. I'm like nobody said anything, you know
No, no if he's ended it as a reason
There's always a reason yeah, it's okay. It's different Chris Chris. You're not monetized. He's monetized. It's different, you know
Right, I'm just trying to keep my channel. I always keep my channel
Be happy for you know, I say even if like off of my channel even if I'm like, you know, I
on the down it out I
Know I'll be able to like, you know keep my channel going and like
No people and like, you know
It leaves me connections figure out they all are able to handle things better
Everything goes to shit. Hey, sir. Did you smoke weed? Are you stoned? What's up? Yeah? I just
Mean do you take like do you take fucking meds you got meds you take meds? No, I don't think
I'm a drug I have like four five almost four five
Not kid list. I'm kidding
You seems like Chris you seem like you're into Percocets, bro. You got any perks
No, I don't it's a I am I'm actually in a per like bike it in per se. Okay. Oh, you got bikes
You got you got some bikes so much. I don't I don't I'm trying to get some you know
I mean like it's hard to find it's hard to find nowadays because everybody's got the fake fucking fentanyl
If you need some good shit my boy boiled down there his his girl is a doctor
She can get you whatever you need
Boyle just get her the script get the script out of her purse. So we'll take care of the rest
Yeah
We'll write our own shit
Yeah, I mean fucking I used to like uh, I
Mean, I do I like Viking in like salt like muscle relaxers
But it's hard you know people fucking they have like a little fucking fake little presses
What's that shit ketamine you ever have ketamine is that the one that a fucking muscle relax it
Like a horse tranquilizer some way where that's way more, but yeah, no, I don't fuck around with that, but
You know it's hard to find prescription can I get some prescription extra strength Viking over here, please real quick
Okay, good luck with that. Yeah, you know, I mean it's like fuck
Yeah, that's true
That's what they say
I mean, I you know my hair Vegas and people are like, man, I got some oxies dog
I'm going to like a panty express this guy's out there. Hey, you want some oxy dog? I'm like
It's fake bullshit. He's like those bombs on the Vegas trip. I want to buy shit from those guys. No, I didn't on the strip
I mean, it's by my fucking. I'm often, you know over here, but
It's like fucking I can't trust on the street, you know any any any any street drugs you're buying Vegas
You can guarantee they were up their ass all day
That's where they fucking store all this shit up their ass, right?
So if you like snort and coke that smells like ass fucking goes right ahead. You'll get all you need
Don't sniff the brown coke
Right. Well, I'm just you know, there is like no
Which is probably I'm probably better off, you know, if I you know if I don't have any fucking like a viking and connect
It's probably better off dude, type shit, you know what I mean, so it's probably better, it's probably better.
Yeah, yeah, drugs is good, I agree, pie.
I like, I like, I like, but you know, I'll be, I'll drink beers and I'll just like, I don't like swallow the, if I have Vicodin's, I don't swallow them, I like chew them up, and then fucking chug it back.
I always drink beer with it, because I like to get, I like to get fucked.
Oh yeah, alcohol and drugs, yeah, that's a good mix.
Hydra hydrocodone or whatever it's called me. That's my shit. I like painkillers muscle relaxers
Oxycontin is basically like the pharmaceutical great heroin. That's not the real JC. That's a clone
But yeah, I'm probably better off to not fucking have like having any any of that fucking
Oh boy, oh, she knows trust me she knows
Thailand all three
Coding hell yeah all day all fucking I know there was a time all three
I was so deep on t-30s dude. I took like five bro. Oh, yeah, I was like this was like ten years
Oh, yeah, Jay, she say something in French, then
T3 yeah, yeah, Jimmy passed out again. This is the panel now for the rest of the night
Yeah, T3's are bomb, bro fucking coding new
It's not gonna be a banger like last night with us Sebastian. Oh
Isaiah made it up here, too. Wow
A pie. Can you come up? Please? I'm surrounded by dudes. I don't need this
That's not up for this shit, you know, that's not how you like come up your your Friday's
I said, wait, where the fuck you going now, dude? You're always doing something. Where you going, dude? I'm on my way home
Where were you before?
Uh, I stopped at my buddy's house just now.
He's going right over the beach.
Marty!
He's right down on the beach.
Franchise d'Otoire.
That is it.
D'Otoire.
Franchise d'Otoire.
Je m'appelle Loupe.
Merci beaucoup.
Yeah, I know life is short bro. Enjoy your shit. You know what I mean? I'm happy. I'm happy. I'm happy right now, type shit.
You gotta be happy, dude. You gotta be fucking happy.
Jaycee, get your ass up here then. Say hi. Come up and say hi. Don't be a bitch that fucking just hangs down this lower check. Come on up.
She could be way worse, bro. You know what I mean? I know how worse it is, dude.
BN suit.
He's back there. He's doing something back there.
BN.
He's frying the sandwich.
Yeah, I think you're right, Boyle
Big French
I got kicked out of French I made it through
We just kept saying we we we we yep and laughing the whole time
French teacher didn't want to teach a child
You'd be 14 years old and say it was a problem
I gotta get down to the spot bro. This will give me like hell it's free shit here. Hey Chris 1995 call
They want their bid back. I know right?
Oh Chris, I wait I can't see the beard. Oh god Fred Durst. Hell yeah
he's all about the nookie
the art bell's grave
oh art bell
is he in the body?
art bell
east of the Rockies
Nevada
oh shit
I mean I got the
coldest of the Rockies
look I don't understand listen I don't understand
how people get the fucking name of the state wrong
I've never said it wrong
It's Nevada Nevada Nevada Nevada Nevada Nevada Nevada Nevada Nevada
It's Nevada. Yeah, that's Vegas, Nevada
Literally, why do people why do people like how do you fucking interpret the word?
We live near the area 51
No, it's area 51.
The bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the bad, the
I've never said it wrong.
I'm from Cali, Doug, and I fucking,
when I was younger, like in my teens,
I come to Vegas, and I've always like,
I've known it, I know the way to say it, Nevada.
Nevada, dude.
Like, is it that hard?
To be fair.
To be fair, yeah.
I almost want to slap people, dude.
It's fucking so tough.
You say, I mean, you're from the West, though, already,
though, so you're already in that area, right?
So I'm like an East Coast piece of shit like me.
We're like, Nevada, right?
Alright, you already got the leg up. You already live in that area, right?
Like you already know how it's enunciated because you definitely encountered people from Nevada and fucking Cali.
Where's Artville's grave?
You know, you know, it's kind of like the uh, uh, uh, like half the rest, like Europe.
Who do we got? Who's behind the wall?
Is it a paywall?
It looked like somebody was coming up.
But, yeah, it's the same shit.
We get some pussy up here, please. Hello. Yeah, no shit calling any pussy down there. Come on up
Yeah, it doesn't help when like fucking, you know, Nevada is on the news about
Whatever, you know, and people talking on a news you're like the bottle. I'm just like, dude. Fuck. Are you stupid?
Were you there when those youtubers were killed? No, but I knew who they were
Uh, like I said, I knew who they were and fucking, uh, it, you know, just like fucking right here on YouTube. They were like, uh, the dude that got shot was striking the other guy's channel. Yeah.
They were all YouTubers here in Vegas and fucking, it was a YouTube fucking beef, dude, that this full fucking guy was from California. He killed the husband and wife that was fucking with him.
Go ahead Chris let him know
Please
No, I'm saying like fucking
It was a YouTube beef that they had like over fucking like years and shit and this that's a full manny fucking is like
He's from Cali. He's like a fucking, you know, Mexican like bottle like what's up homes? I don't play
He's I guarantee he's probably got felonies
He's been to prison and he doesn't fuck around like just like I don't fuck around either
If I say something to somebody like fucking on the internet like I will back it up in real life tech shit
And he's the same way and fucking, you know, it's, I can't believe it.
You're gonna get life without parole, easy.
I mean, maybe the death penalty.
What happened?
That's what I mean.
Like, I don't know shit about the story.
Well, that's basically it.
They were fighting for years and they were going back and forth.
It was just streamer beef, YouTube shit.
Yeah, that's it.
That's it.
They kept breaking his channel.
Did he like he shot him or he thought he had what what do you have Chris? He had like 4,000 subscribers
It was bullshit both of them had like 4,000 maybe 8,000 each
Forget I forget the subs but like
Right in front of Bellagio up by the fountain show, you know, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right
We're streaming and they had the tripods the camera set up
Him and his big-mouth wife, they both
I mean, you know what no fuck fuck fuck though if you think that people if you think you're untouchable, right?
Fucking fuck that. It's the internet. I know everybody talks some big bullshit fucking game
But you'll catch that motherfucker every once in a while. Yeah, you get a cycle. That's it. It's over. Yeah, it's done
I mean, I
You know, if somebody wants to come at me with the shit that I say or whatever the fuck
But I'm not gonna threaten you and say I'm coming to you. Oh, I got enough time for that shit
I got enough money that Lola would want to come see me
But at the same point though, I mean
I ain't talking shit to every mother fucker on here, you know, I have a disrespect. I don't I mean if I say you know
I don't really I don't say anything to anybody, you know
I'm pretty uh
It'd be fucked up if his wife didn't know anything about it and she ended up getting kept no
I mean what happened like if you watch the video like what happened like
She noticed I'm walking up. He's like he don't come around here
He's like don't come around here trying to start some shit and then the other guy walked
He's like what's up cuz and he's like pop pop pop five shots and one guy
And then she's like, she's like, are you fucking kidding me?
Yes, yes, that's right.
He threw the gun on her and he's like, he blasted her.
Got shot in the chest.
I think that he threw a second shot on the headshot.
And then she drops the camera.
Oh, fuck it, dude.
You know, you got to go, you got to go.
That's it.
I ain't going to justify that bullshit,
but I mean, like, I mean, don't fucking run your mouth
when you don't, you know, respect the fucking outcome,
right?
Like, you don't know the motherfucker
you're talking to on the other end, right?
Like, Chris, I ain't going to pipe off to you, right?
I don't know if you are crazy enough to find me and fucking show up here, right?
That's what I'm saying, like chat, anybody watching, this is like a wake-up call for
fucking, you know what I mean? Watch what you say, the motherfuckers, because some people don't play.
Like, they don't give a fuck.
The guy was like, fuck it, I'll just go to prison.
That's it, and he fucking did the two people dead.
We both said we don't play, but I already said,
I'm way too lazy to go find him on the fucker,
and I'm too cheap,
because I ain't gonna spend my fucking hard-earned money
on trying to fucking fly to Cali
or wherever I'm gonna fucking beat somebody's ass for it.
No bullshit, right?
But come to me, come to me, Stefan,
I'm gonna fucking, I'm gonna put you fucking down.
Where you at, I said, where you at?
I'm gonna try to put you down.
Where you at, dude?
Let us let everyone know where you are
Ohio search I am I am one of one. I stream with my real fucking name or I'm on with my real name
I'm very easy to find
In Ohio
Absolutely, I don't even need to say Ohio.
Nobody's going to Ohio, dude.
Fuck Ohio.
I know, exactly.
You get stuck here, it sucks.
You're safe, you're fucking safe.
Yeah, you're safe.
Ohio fucking sucks, bro.
At least if you go to Vegas,
you're gonna have a good time
before you go to jail at Ohio.
I ain't even trying to go to Vegas.
I ain't a gambler.
I mean, I do want to eat in Vegas, though.
I'm a fat fuck.
I want that buffet life, dog.
I think it's got the best buffet. No, no, they don't actually not anymore. Vegas used to be the shit. There's still some good ones. There's still some good ones. Yeah, very few, but you can pay like 150 bucks.
150 bucks for a buffet. Fuck that. 30 bucks in a bucket, you know, but it's like. Where? Circus. Circus, dude, you might as well eat out of the dumpster.
You're me. You're me. You are the trash third circus. Oh dude. Oh dude. I live in the dumpster all day long. You tell me I get king crab legs in the dumpster
Dude, point me in the right fucking direction. I'm just
Yeah, like what up?
Plums you
Plums you said you're gonna get a hug buddy
Yeah, you can. Hi, Psyche. Hi, how are you?
Members and non-members, everybody a hug, but members all hug a little tighter.
Virtual hugs. Psyche, are you a found mine right now?
I don't know how it sounded like it yet.
All right, fair enough.
I don't want to.
It's like, you don't have to worry.
You don't have to worry.
I don't want to.
I don't want to say much.
It's not going to be a repeater last night.
Don't worry.
Yeah.
I don't want to deprive my shit and you're not.
No, I, you know.
I love it.
Guys.
Sometimes it's like there's a ghost.
I love you.
Well, there's people putting someone backstage, and I'm bringing them up, and when I was asleep and I'm like, well, it's impossible, but it happens when I'm asleep.
I don't know, there's a ghost that takes care of the show somehow, so it's not me, if you, like, feel like you're kicked off, or if there's, like, some kind of ghost that's wearing the show.
I don't know, I don't know who it is.
I don't know. I'm not saying shit. I'm just not gonna. I'm not gonna see her.
I don't know if you're not here. Alright, that's all I'm saying. I ain't gonna be
No, I'm not. No, I'm all here. Oh, even tried. We all good. You're mad at me. I'm not mad at
you and I don't. I'm doing it. I swear. I didn't do anything. Being gangsta here.
Guys, but I donated five memberships today. Who got you looking at membership? I saw somewhere we got a membership
A few other people we guys we had like 25 member memberships
If you would like to do this in memberships, that'd be awesome
I think I'm all tapped out for the week
but uh
I did donate like probably 10 to two memberships
Yeah, if you'd like to
If you'd like to be a viewer and you'd like to support if you'd like to support psych
on here dude like you'd appreciate that don't like any type of donation. Yeah, I would think yeah, and
No, but also I want to do readings for people. I don't want to just ask for donations
I want to like offer service for people. So of course if you've had a donation or whatever
donation donation
People fucking watch this type shit, you know, I mean fucking so they fucking you know fucking you know
And you're fucking going on your way. You're stressed out. I mean, I'll you know fucking you chat
You see this the viewers you see like how many how many people fucking are hating on fucking this guy over here
Trying to fucking make his channel bigger. It's crazy, right like fuck
the
They've made me fucking be fat. Yeah, fucking do something better dude. I know
Take that
Sitting in your fucking house trying to hate on this guy dude on the internet dude. How about that?
Viewers
Hated on this fucking guy dude. He's trying to fucking like better himself like whatever dude. I mean, that's that's what I say
Thank you so much. Yeah, it's yeah as I really oh look at the cat
White cat. Oh boy. Yeah, you gotta better yourself. Otherwise. What's the point?
Yeah, that's what it's about. And you know what? I've heard better myself. It's like, you know, some people are
Some people are given like a feeling of no hope and it's they give no hope
Then what reason is there to better yourself?
So if you're giving a little bit of hope if you're giving a little bit of like
forgive this people will better themselves and they change but if really there's no hope if
people will never forgive them if people will just judge them and look at them the same way
no matter what they do then what motivations are for people to change so how about we like you know
if people try to change we give them a little bit of like you know
forgiveness because we've all made mistakes in our lives and
Listen like make your own make start streaming on your own channel, dude
Or whatever like these people that fucking are trying to like, you know, bring you down like do your own shit
Stay in this house
You're gonna have to sleep with Rocky for a month
You don't want to do it mongo you can leave
You gotta give them tough love. Hey crystal
Hey, buddy, remember when you used to threaten rape and like threaten
Killing all the time. I
Remember how bad like things would go for me and like I don't like I don't like falls from grace at one point
Like you guys were saying all these bad things
against my entire life saying bad things like
People that I wasn't even you were saying that I was going to a black man remember when you said I was married to a black man
And that you were saying that I hope you get raped and killed
on a daily basis
He's using a well are you using a well 2.0 much you get here are you using 2.0 or 3.0?
Probably your shit's frozen man. Your motor must be fucked
Chris I would never tell anyone to rape you you don't have to worry about that
Well, you've already done it because you've already done it
Well, you can't
These are the people like I've given you like one second of a breath and then you always look it up for everything
But that's these people because these people you let these people believe anything these people are devil worse first and
You think that anything is great from them. It's all bad
You know
Yeah, I'm God
I'm God you could worship me right now
100% I don't think so I 100% do new
Oh, you, yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Hey, what's up? What are you doing disrespectful shit? Yeah. No, listen. Give a give give her a second give her a second
What are you doing right now, Chris? You know, she's doing
Guess what
Listen, calm up, calm up, what, you don't know how to hold your phone right?
What's the problem?
No, listen, they like sniced up on my nose, like they like made my nose look huge.
They put my birthmark, like my tiny birthmark, like it's 28 times thousand times.
You know, you never make anything stop.
But you know what?
That NorCal, his wife is fat as fuck.
What are you talking about?
What birthmark?
NorCal
NorCal beats his wife and his show
you know his family members and
He is like mad because I he abuses me as like a shield
For beating his children
I think you're tripping out, I think you can actually see it in proof because you know how intuitive you are
Well, you know, I mean I fucking say I don't even look up look up fucking North cow
And his fat wife, she looks, they both have red hair.
They're both fat and he has four kids and two retards
and three he doesn't take care of.
I don't even know what that is, but all right.
Go with that, go with that.
And he, you know, parent, fat parent, he wants their polka-dotted panties.
Can you bring that in the sands?
He asked for Karen's polka dotted panties.
Imagine him asking.
Not only did he ask for Karen's panties,
he asked for a fucking betas and chicken snakes.
Snakes, cakes, he asked for a fucking pig.
I'll do it.
Like this fucking guy, he looks like a fucking fat pig.
And nor, he's making me, like he puts me as like a snowshell.
Yeah, what do you think about a good times you got bad you got bad make I
Don't I don't know I didn't know that but can we make sure that?
Because that guy like I told you that guy
You let that girl up
Yeah, that girl we don't the fuck that means
Actually, we don't actually know exactly
You know exactly what it means any we know exactly and we have FBI on the case
Okay, well, I'm sure FBI can handle it more than this fucking panel can correct. Yeah, cuz we have CPI
I don't know what the fuck you're talking about. I think FBI can handle it more than us, correct
Well, we're talking about critical I mean, I don't know that crowbar that girl by my hand
Let's be thrilled. What the fuck are you talking about?
What do you always come up talking the same dumb ass shit? Oh my gosh
oh
My god
What's up, okay, but you should look on number see I can speak the same language
What if you're not the fuck you're talking about? Maybe you should be quiet.
You really don't know anything about life. You don't really know anything about life.
I don't know anything about life. I don't know anything about you. Come on, dum-dum.
You don't need to speak English. You're too stupid to have the conversation. You don't know what the fuck's going on
You're setting their mother and I'm not calling your name if I called your name
I told you a horror if I do that did I did I call you whore? Well, you are dumb dumb
That's straight mark by me by the way, but I
Hey, oh my gosh
Do it together we'll do it together Chris K. We'll do it together
Yeah, we'll do it together. We'll do it together, dude
Fuck that guy
You are fucking right now you are a dumb dumb man
Hey, can I ask you something you don't know shit about Chris guy
Crystal can I ask you a question right there in Hollywood crystal a friend of mine, right?
There's a friend of mine is a friend of mine. He's dating this girl. She has a 16 year old son
She has a she has a 16 year old son, right? And he's a little autistic and she wants him to move in with her
But he doesn't want to commit because this kid's a little like crazy
And he has his own kids. What do you think you should do? You think you should just move in with her?
Or you should like just leave and go somewhere else
You want me to rephrase the question
Well, you rephrase yourself in the question.
You say you're a child as a 14-year-old want to be a child.
No, I said I said 16.
Treated like another person.
The woman has a 16-year-old son.
Listen, bitch, you heard the question correct.
Should the guy move in with her?
Should you move in with her?
I'm not doing your fucking family.
It has nothing to do with me.
I'm talking about a friend of mine.
Yeah, you have a problem.
You have a problem, buddy.
You have a problem.
And it has nothing to do.
Boy, you know, what the fuck was that?
Oh, holy shit.
You got to kill the stream, Isaiah just fucking porn bomb the whole fucking stream, man.
Put it away, bro, put it away.
I don't know if that was a fucking cat or a mac and cheese. What are you doing?
Ah shit, you're a fucking kid. They only want to be talked about good, you know
Who?
What's so negative she's always so negative I never hear anything sweet coming out of her mouth God you're fucking bully
Goss, what's your name goss?
Listen, I'm not a bully gossed
Thank you are sir. Who told you that?
Well me I told myself that
Why why do you have two ghosts in your name like ghost crucible ghosts like that's a little redundant?
What does that do with the point? Well, the point is that you're being redundant right got you on that one didn't
You lost you already lost you don't even know it listen. Don't leave your church
Me
The bad guy is always gonna be the bad guy to the day dies, okay?
This guy is never gonna fucking roll out to be the fucking good guy, okay?
This guy's always gonna be a fucking piece of shit
Who I say he's cool
He doesn't bother anybody really
Thomas
Oh, he's not that one guy
Little attention whore, maybe
No, it's not that guy. It's not that guy you're thinking about the morning on another panel night
No, it's time to debate panel, but I'm gonna
We're you talking about that that boy
Who you know the panel I'm talking about who?
Free
Oh bronze bird TPP
Yeah, it's fucking one go over there. If you don't believe it go over there. I'm like, I just
Looked at us for less hour
Yeah, they're still live now. I just looked at us for the last hour
Yeah, the problem with that is goes there getting too big for their bridges over there, you know
They got a little radio show going on. I don't know if you've seen it
Eli has this live little radio show going on. I think I've seen it all the guests are on it now
They might have you on that ass live
I would be on there too. No
Would you like me to would you like to debate?
No, no, I don't know debate
There's no point I always let's run that bitch dog. I don't I don't do that stuff. No, I'm sorry
That's why you join panels like this no, I know exactly what I'm talking about. I'm God
Yeah, good debate you fucking you don't have got in your life to your ghost. You're just wandering around from panel to panel
He's saying it's from that back. Let's have a debate. Let's have a little debate
Crystal won't you settle down with Isaiah?
Why don't you settle down with that? No, no, I don't I don't want I say you should settle down with Isaiah
Make you happy. Definitely
Without Jamie you guys could be happy, you know, yeah, you'd settle down good with a psyche or Jamie or
Yeah, why don't you settle down with like why don't you sort of almost like not
No, you're not gonna talk over here. She just asked you that question. Why don't you sort of almost like he's like he's taken
He's got easy. He's got Alex. No
He's got you want to be I could I could name another
So I mean we couldn't do the same run. Yeah, let's go run run
You guys trying to tag team is this what you're doing
Are you trying to team up against God right now?
You have to team up against God? You're gonna lose.
Soon as Crystal shuts up, I'm gonna burn that ass up.
You're gonna lose. You're gonna lose.
I'm down.
I'll just call my boys. I don't have to lose.
You're gonna lose, Crystal. You're gonna lose.
You'll lose in the long run.
I might lose tonight, but I might, because I don't care.
To win and go to bed and fuck off. Nobody cares in the long run. You might win
You might win you might win be gone. You might win. You might win if he tried
Fuck off take a fucking chance in life
Now I go to bed. Don't play it safe
Yeah, I know back to the kitchen
You're
Are we now what back to the kitchen? You don't the fuck you're talking about
Are you drunk or are you stupid what's your favorite cooking both
What drunk and stupid
I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I
My gosh, please don't you're the most in person person jump somebody. I'll be
Hey back. I already told you back be gone
This person's gonna hurt you. Does anybody have some silver?
This person has my back. I don't know me. I'm
Master here with some silver brother
Back you miss me, huh? I know you miss me you filthy creature yellow flower
You know what the cross means back
My
Salmon is for old people like over 60 you got me sober on you if you don't mind that's disgusting
She's gonna have to go to bed and I have to use sober. I could go for some
That was sweet
And I'm not gonna hear anything else you say cuz I'm gonna take that as like you'd love us
No, no, no, no too late
Can kick her out psych you know what you know what I'll even fucking make the point and psyche will agree with me
I'll fucking defend you
I'll literally debate this guy. If you say he didn't stay, if you say he didn't stay, I'll fucking say he didn't get rid of him.
Say he didn't stay. You don't have to leave.
He's what we call in the army a mirage.
No, no, no, fuck that.
No, she wants to say it and say I have her back.
When you get close to her,
talk shit about her,
see what you're really prepared for.
I'll be right, it's coming out.
It's a mirage, it's a mirage.
She's not a strong and important independent woman?
Mirage.
I got her back.
She wants me to have her back, I got it.
I know none of you can defeat me in my argument, so it's one that looks like a lady.
You're not gonna debate me.
Come on girl, you're more than welcome to join.
Well, I'd like to book by this cover.
Well, who you gonna love by your lover?
You say love do me twice. You got the bitch in the rice
So you're just seeing like every target
She likes it likes it likes it likes it. Did she leave
Well, that's that I
Don't okay, man. Did she
What's your problem
Bitch you just literally you literally heard the question I just asked I will slap you're the one that took offense to it
You I swear you're the one that took offense. I will slap the ghost off of you
You gonna slap nothing you know better keep it up kid
They keep it up, bitch. You know better. No, actually, I missed that boil. You do know better
You're not that dumb dumb, you know better, I don't know better
You're not gonna slap me. No, what you said was
You know, but no
You know better what you said what I don't give a fuck what you're looking at
What you said was gonna slap you ain't gonna slap nothing, you know, that kid don't work on God you fool
You know better you might as well stop right now
You know better you're embarrassing yourself, dude
I'm not embarrassing nothing. You know better. Yeah, you're embarrassed never do it. All right, you would never look at Isaiah
He's embarrassed for you would never do it. You would never slept you would never do it
Yeah, okay, you know better. What's your smart?
Yeah, it's very smart. I mean, okay. Yeah, I was saying you know, yeah, yeah. Yeah, that's right. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, you know better
You know better. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you know better. Oh, yeah, I know that. Yeah, you would actually never even try to
Oh, you know what? You know what? You know what happens? You know what? I would fucking ask, I would destroy you. Oh, wow
I can't believe we're in total agreement. Would you like to do it now? I agree with you. Would you like to do it now?
Wow, you know what? You're right. You're not gonna do it, are you? You are 100% correct, pal. You never outdebate me.
I have never spoken to someone as great as you.
So you never do it. You've got to be one of the most honest people I've ever met.
All right, be quiet then.
Don't sit down, be a bait, and shut the fuck up. It's okay.
All right. Okay, good work. Be quiet.
This is great. Great talk.
Shh.
Great conversation.
You know, you've never...
Great conversation with a dumb talk.
Yeah, quiet with yourself.
With a dumb-dumb.
Now you ain't talking to a dumb-dumb like that.
Dumb-dumb?
You're not gonna use my word
How many times I gotta own you dumb dumb. I mean check the score brother
Go ahead and make your argument
You're you're gonna have to make your argument dumb dumb dumb dumb
How is that an argument
I'm confused. Oh, how is that how is that an argument?
dumb dumb
How's that an argument dumb dumb?
My win that dumb
Dumb god, Jim. I just keep winning dumb. Yeah, bro. You need a chain. I just keep winning dumb dumb
Dumb dumb
Where the fuck are you going I say what are you getting your steps in for the day? You haven't stopped moving for like two hours
You're muted you're fucking muted. I can't hear you
Yeah, I win
You just walking in circles in the house
You win go ghost by the way you won I
Did win thank you. Yeah, you won you won. Yeah, absolutely. All right. Thank you brother. You want in life easy work
He's your life. You're a winner. You are a winner ghost
You are a winner. Don't let anybody tell you you're a loser
Because you're a hundred percent a winner
Isaiah you muted you just talking to yourself at this point
Yeah, you can't fix it I
Know he's making me dizzy
Yeah, yeah, I don't really lips
No, no, that's for psyche yeah save it for psyche
Five-hour marathon you should I I could I think you think he's asleep
All right, I'm gonna get ready. Hold on. Give me two seconds
All right, here we go.
Okay, here we go.
You ready?
Revelation chapter 19 verse 5
And a voice came out of the throne saying praise God
And I heard it as it were the voice of a great multitude, and as the voice of many waters,
and as the voice of mighty thunderings, saying, Alleluia for the Lord God omnipotent reigneth.
And to her was granted that she should be arrayed in fine linen, clean and white,
for the first linen is the righteous of saints, and he saith unto me, Right.
Blessed are they which are called unto marriage, supper of the Lamb.
And he saith unto me, These are the true sayings of God.
And I fell at his feet to worship him.
And he said unto me, See thou do it not.
worship God for the testimony of Jesus is the spirit of prophecy.
His eyes were as flame of fire and on his head were many crowns and he had a
name written that no man knew but he himself and he was clothed with a
vesture dipped in blood and his name is called the Word of God.
and the armies which were in heaven followed him upon white horses,
clothed in fine linen, white and clean. And out of his mouth goeth a sharp sword,
that with his teeth should smite the nations, and he shall rule them with a rod of iron,
and he treadeth with wine-press of fierceness and wrath of Almighty God.
And he hath on his vesture and on his thigh a name written, King of kings and Lord of lords.
And I saw an angel standing in the sun and he cried with a loud voice saying to all the fowls that fly,
that ye may eat the flesh of kings and the flesh of captains and the flesh of mighty men
and the flesh of horses and help them that sit on them.
the flesh of all men both free and bond both small and great and I saw the
beast and the kings of the earth and their armies gathered together to make
war against him that sat on the horse and against his army and the beast was
taken and with him the false prophet that wrought miracles before him with
which he deceived them that had received the mark of the beast and them that
the remnant were slain with a sword of him that sat upon the horse, which sword
proceeded out of his mouth and all the fowls were filled with their flesh. And I
saw an angel come down from heaven, having the key of the bottomless pit and a
great chain in his hand, and he laid hold on the dragon, the old serpent which is
the devil and Satan.
bound him a thousand years and cast him into the bottomless pit and shut him up
and set a seal upon him that he should receive the nations no more till the
thousand years should be fulfilled and after that he must be loosed a little
upon the land and I saw thrones and they sat upon them and judgment was given
unto them and I sat the souls that were break beheaded for the witness of Jesus
which had not worshiped the beast. Neither his image, neither his received his mark
upon the foreheads, or in their hands, and they lived and reigned with Christ a
thousand years. But the rest of the dead lived not again until the thousand years
were finished. This is the first resurrection. Death hath no power, but
they shall be priests of God and of Christ, and shall reign with him a thousand
Satan shall be loosed out of his prison, and shall go out to deceive the nations which
are in four quarters of the earth, Gog and Magog, to gather them to battle, the number
of whom is at the sand of the sea.
And they went up to the breath of the earth and compassed at the camp of the saints about.
And the devil that deceived them was cast into the lake of fire and brimstone, where the beast and the false prophet are, and are tormented day, every day, night.
And I saw a great white throne, and him that sat on it, from whose face the earth and the heaven fled away, and there was found no place for them.
And I saw the dead, small and great, stand before God, and the books were opened, and another book was opened, which is the book of life.
And the dead were judged out of those things which were written in the books according to their works.
And the sea gave up the dead which were in it.
And the dead held delivered up the dead which were in them.
And they were judged every man according to their works.
And the death and hell were cast into the lake of fire.
This is the second death.
And whosoever was not found written to the book of life was cast into the lake of fire.
I saw a new heaven and a new earth for the first heaven and the first earth were passed away and
There was no more sea and I saw John
The holy city knew Jerusalem coming down from God out of heaven
Prepared as a bride adorned for her husband
And I heard a great voice out of heaven saying behold the tabernacle of God is with men
And he will dwell with them, and they shall be his people, and God himself shall be with
them, and be their God.
Neither shall there be any more pain, for the former things are passed away."
I make all things new, and He said unto me, Right, for these words are true and faithful.
And He said unto me, It is done.
I am Alpha and Omega, the beginning and the end.
I will give unto Him that is a thirst for the fountain of water of life freely.
And He that overcomes shall inherit all things, and I will be His God, and He shall be my
But the fearful and unbelieving and the abominable and murderers and whore mongers and sorcerers and idolaters and all the liars
Shall be burned to death in brimstone, which is their second death
And there came unto me one of seven angels which had the seven vials
Full of the seven last plagues and talked with me saying come hither
I will shoe thee the bride, the lamb's wife, and he carried me away in the spirit to a
great high mountain, and shewed me that great city, the holy Jerusalem, descending out of
heaven from God.
Having the glory of God and her light was like unto a stone most precious, even like
a jasper stone, clear as crystal.
At the gates, twelve angels, and names written thereon, which are the names of the twelve tribes of the children of Israel.
On the east, three gates. On the north, three gates. On the south, three gates. And on the west, three gates.
And the wall of the city had twelve foundations, and in them the names of the twelve apostles of the Lamb.
And that talked with me had a golden reed to measure the city.
and the gates thereof, and the wall thereof, and the city of Leith, fourth square, and
the length is as large as the breadth, and he measured the city with the reed twelve
thousand furlongs, and he measured the wall thereof in hundred forty and four cubits,
according to the measure of a man that is of the angel, and the building of the wall
and the city was pure gold unto clear glass, and the foundations of the wall were garnished
with all manner of precious stones.
The first foundation was Jasper, the second Sapphire, the third Chalcedony, the fourth
Emerald, the fifth Sardonyx, the sixth Sadeus, the seventh Chrysalite, the eighth Beryl, the
Every several gate was woven of pearl, and the street of the city was pure gold, as it
were transparent glass, and I saw no temple therein, for the Lord God Almighty and the
Lamb are the temple of it, and the city had no need of the sun, neither of the moon to
shine in it, for the glory of God did lighten it, and the Lamb is the light thereof, and
and the kings of the earth do bring their glory and honor unto it.
And the gates of it shall not be shut at all by day, for there shall be no night there,
and they shall bring the glory and honor of the nations unto it, and there shall in no
wise enter into anything that defileeth.
Neither whatsoever worketh abomination, nor maketh a lie, but the which thou written in
And he shooed me pure river of water of life, clear as crystal, proceeding out of the throne
of God and of the Lamb.
In the midst of the street of it, and on either side of the river, was there the tree of life,
which bared twelve manner of fruits, and yielded her fruit every month, and the leaves of the
tree were of the healing of the nations, and there shall be no more curse, but the throne
And there shall see his face, and his name shall be in their foreheads.
And there shall be no night there.
They need no candle, no light of the sun, for the Lord God giveth them light, and they shall
reign forever and ever.
And he said unto me, These sayings are faithful and true.
And the Lord God of the Holy Prophet sent his angel to shoo unto his servants the things
which must shortly be done.
Behold, I come quickly.
Blessed is he that keepeth the sayings of the prophecy of this book.
And I John saw these things and heard them, and when I heard and seen I fell down to worship
before the feet of the angel which should be these things.
Then sayeth he unto me, See, thou do it not, for I am thy fellow servant, and of thy brethren the prophets, and of them which keep the sayings of this book worship God.
And he sayeth unto me, Seal not the sayings of the prophecy of this book, for the time is at hand.
He that is unjust, let him be unjust still, and he which is filthy, let him be filthy still.
and He that is righteous, let Him be righteous still, and He that is holy, let Him be holy still.
I am Alpha and Omega, the beginning and the end, the first and the last, blessed are Thy that do His commandments,
that they may have right to the tree of life and may enter in through the gates into the city.
For without dogs are sorcerers and whoremongers and murderers and idolaters and whosoever's
loveth and maketh a lie, I, Jesus, have sent my angel to testify unto these things, to
the churches.
I
crashed out.
That's it.
Ah, shit. Did he pray? I didn't see him.
Was he honest? I said, did you pray to that shit?
Good for you, man. You're going straight to heaven.
You'll be the only one tonight. Everybody else, they're going to hell.
Especially you, A-cat. You're going straight to hell, bitch.
You know what's fucked up? It was over. All I had was another page to go.
And then I just blew it at the end fuck it I'll have to start from the beginning hold on
Yes, you would memorize some dumb shit like that
There's stupid book of squiggly lines
Jim's making money off this all your selling tapes Jim good for you, man
20 bucks. That's not bad. I get half that. I
Don't know what he's doing. I'm not even watching me. He's in the dark now
Isaiah you've been on mute the whole time
Sike you must have fucked your thing up. Oh, it's not working at all. It was like he did it. Oh shit, dude
You know what check your volume. It might be your volume now. It's not your volume
Then your shit out of luck, bro
Thanks for hanging out you might as well get some cards. You can write down stuff on cards
Mr. Gotti brainwash me
You mean why are you so negative?
Geez I'm reading from the Bible and you're being negative. What's wrong with you?
You just come here to be negative?
This I'm not I'm not Sebastian. I'm not gonna speak for six hours straight
Maybe another six minutes and I will call it a night
Psych definitely passed out either. He doesn't have to worry about any pictures. I'm not gonna post any pictures up here. I
Don't do that kind of thing
I'm not about the pictures
Well, maybe one maybe just one this was the picture of the night by the way everyone this is my favorite
You are one lucky guy
Dude she wraps her lips around that and just fucking slowly pulled it out. I
Bet she doesn't do that for you though
She got mad when I said that I thought Mungo watches her while she's in the shower.
I think I went a little too far with that one.
Oh, does she? Oh, nice. Yeah, do that. She's the key for that.
Just have her get rid of that face piercing.
Did she get mad? Oh, shit.
Well, I guess we we found her limit
She talks a good game, but in the end I guess we knew she couldn't hang
Now every time she takes a shower she's gonna look what's to say I pissed someone off
Yeah, what you do what you say to him?
Is that why you ended the stream earlier because of you?
Poor guy's got a right to sit down now
Oh, I better take this picture off before she sees it.
What does it say? I can't see.
Jim? Oh, I'm just here. Oh, yeah. You're just here, pal. Thanks. I appreciate the support.
He's taking a dump.
Go put the phone by the door, and I'll talk to her while she's taking a dump
Let me know when you're over there
Put it put it right up against the door
She's gonna hear my voice. Let me know give me a signal
Hurry up, hurry up, you know, you know women don't fucking sit on the toilet too long
Good you me good good take your fucking Chinese ass the fuck out of here. I
Liked your gospel. Thanks, bro. Appreciate it. That was the revelation of God
Almost got through with it, too
Really she's up already dude she took a shit it was like one minute
Did she even wipe?
Yeah, I'm triggered. I'm triggered when I see you you slanty-eyed bitch
No, no, no, he doesn't do meth meth makes you skinny
That's um, that's signal you're thinking about
Signal does math
You me you are loser you are the loser you come here to see me. I don't go anywhere to see you you lose
You the biggest loser you lie about baby you lie about husband you lie about Islam you lie about Quran
You lie, are you big lie, are you me? You lie, lie, lie.
Oh, what, like four months ago?
She's, get over yourself.
And the only reason you go to Doug's is so fucking boring there. You don't even like going there.
The only reason you go there is because you can't get up on any other panel.
You're evil. You're the evil one. The way you treat people is only evil people treat people like that
There's no good in you only evil
Who hurt you was it me did I hurt you I
Hurt you when I used to come up on your panel and I call you a dumb dumb
Did you get mad that day?
No, you begged you're the one who begged
Oh, Mr. Gotti, Mr. Gotti, please, Mr. Gotti, show me your pee-pee, show me your pee-pee please, Mr. Gotti, I want to see, I want to see, I want to see your pee-pee, Mr. Gotti, Mr. Gotti, I will love you so much, Mr. Gotti.
And then I showed it to you, and what happened? You fucking fell in love and now you're obsessed.
Big mistake.
Big fucking mistake.
Oh Mr. Gotti! Hey Mr. Gotti! You want to see my underwear Mr. Gotti? I'll show you my
underwear too Mr. Gotti. Oh yeah! You want to see? You want to see my underwear? I'll
show you. I'll show you. Oh is that a lie too Yumi? I bet that was a lie huh? You didn't
do that right? You didn't do that. Oh come on Yumi. Stop lying. Come on. Stop lying.
I botched in chat Puzo. I can't I'm blocked in chat you're blocked in chat also. No, I read it
I read what you wrote
Something about Justin Boyle
Yes, you did you did say it you said you liked it
You mean I was there you said you liked it you said
Oh, Mr. God, yeah, I like your pee pee. I like your pee pee. It's so nice
Your pee pee so nice. I said, thank you, Yumi. I said don't fall in love, but you fell in love
It's a curse. What I
Can't read lips, bro
And plus you're in the dark doesn't make it any easier I
Don't think I psyched in this to you
I think it's on your end, you're gonna have to bang the phone a couple of times, man.
Oh, you know what you do, you gotta hit, you gotta joggle the volume button, and joggle
that a few times, and it's gonna go up.
Let me, let me see if I can do something on this side, okay, that should work.
What did you do? Oh, you blocked him? Oh, it was Boyle who did it, Isaiah.
He shut off your volume. Yeah, he said he did it.
Oh, you know, it was funny though. She never even washed her finger after she did it.
You gotta wonder what's going on there
Mr. Justin, so you didn't know when I was on so Dougie mr. Gotti show up
Mr. Gotti stop lying, okay
No, mr. Justin, no, thanks
It's like he's getting phone calls now. Oh
You left Gaudi up there alone again
Big mistake. No, no, I don't do anything like that. Come on
We love psyche
Well, we'd be without psyche right right Isaiah
We'd be lost
You love psyche right
Yeah, yeah, see
Give one of those give one of those hearts where you put your two hands together and make a heart out of it
Can you do that?
Okay, you can only do one hand
All right, never mind never mind
Yeah, yeah, you have to do it two hands
No, not today or maybe later
I think she's gonna get sick of me real quick boil
We'll just have to find somebody new
ever show you guys my sister picture my sister check this out oh shit boil she
said Stephanie looks like Keith Farron
oh it's fucked up give me what's wrong with you that's fucked up
Oh, you say that
That's my sister not bad, huh
She wasn't my sister I'd hit that
Actually, she said it was cool. I'd still hit it
Yeah, Eli, I don't think so pal. Look again. Look real close. Yeah, she is going to hell for that
Shame on you. Oh
My god, Yumi, I didn't know you became lesbian for Tiffany
Oh, Miss Tiffany. Oh, I love you, Miss Tiffany. Oh, I want to eat your ass. Oh, Miss Tiffany.
Oh, Miss Yumi, eat your ass, Miss Tiffany. Oh, yeah. Oh, Miss Tiffany. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, Miss Tiffany. You give me your cat. Oh, Miss Tiffany. You give me cat. Your cat. Oh, yes. Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah, Miss Tiffany.
You lesbian. You're such a lesbian, Yumi. I didn't know you became a lesbo
You gave up the bullshit about having a husband you just became a big lesbo
Hey, listen bitch, I don't fucking lie. All right, I'm God
God doesn't fucking lie. You lie. You're the liar
God only tells the truth. You got a problem with that. You know what you can do
Eat shit and die
You're the tits of my sister, huh nice she got that fat-ass too
Which cigarette the one where she's smoking a cigarette hold on I don't think I have that one
No, no, no, no, it's just a finger.
This one, this is a good one too.
I only got a few.
Oh, you and me make fun of people in the wheelchair.
That's good.
That's good. That's why your baby is in hell burning in a wheelchair
Okay
See she's negative negative bitch
Where's my picture of you Yumi I must have a picture of you somewhere
Thought I think I got rid of them all
You're corrupting my files. Oh
Here it is. I do have one of you
This was you me about maybe a year ago
She was somewhere complaining about me
There she is
You what are you doing taking a bath? Oh
Mr. God how you get my picture mr. God? Oh, yes, that's me. That's me mr. God. Oh mr. God
You take good picture of me. Oh
Oh, yes, mr. God. Yeah, I look just like a big shit
Big fat piece of shit mr. God
That's you dumb dumb, of course, that's you you stupid
Yeah, get me some fried lice
I want some bonus baribs and some wings
Yeah, you me lucky day. I got rid of all your pictures. I don't have any pictures of you. I
Erased you for my life now why so why are you here trying to get back in?
Why are you begging for my attention
You miss me, huh you really miss me
You know what happened she fell in love with me when I showed her my pic she fell in love with me
Yeah, take a screenshot the face of God that was two years ago
My hair was longer good, I don't care. I don't care let them be bored
Basically the whole channel is about to shut down once I leave. It doesn't matter.
Oh, come on Mr. Justin. You're not on my side. You're not on my side, Mr. Justin. You big liar.
See? Why are you saving my pick with a mask? You're obsessed. You're fucking obsessed with me.
I erased all your pics. I don't even want you on my phone, but you still have me on your phone. Why? Why is that?
Why are you obsessed you me stop being obsessed be a normal one and go away go somewhere new
There are two million people on here. Go find somebody new to fuck with
You know come here no more
You banned
I banned you, you are not normal one, Miss Chyna, fuck you Yumi, fuck you, yes fuck you,
you come here no more, you been here for hour, you waste all my time, you no come here no
FUCK YOU, BITCH!
Oh, oh, Mr. Gotti is God. Yes, Mr. Gotti. Mr. Gotti, you God, Mr. Gotti. Yes, you God.
Oh, you China. Yes, you China. You know fool me. You from China. Yes.
Ah, so. Oh, ah, so, you me. Oh, you have plastic baby. Yes, you have big plastic baby.
I see your plastic baby. You hold your plastic baby and you say this is real baby.
But we don't know real baby. Yes, you have plastic baby. Oh, yes, you big liar. You big, big liar.
Ah, shit.
See what happens when you're on a panel by yourself?
This is basically what happens.
All right, I have to show you this picture.
This is a beautiful picture.
Where do you see this?
I'll give you three guesses.
Who this is?
All right, maybe you can get it in one guess.
Will you tell me who this is?
You saying I'm lying about the wheelchair? What a bitch!
You want evidence, you fucking cunt? I'll give you fucking evidence, you bitch.
Hold on, hold the fuck on, you fucking bitch.
You call me a liar?
You're the fucking liar, bitch.
You want evidence? I'll give you evidence.
Hold on.
Hold on, I took this picture a week ago.
You fucking dumb bitch.
This is a week ago. This is me wearing my new Trump shirt. Look at this
Yep, right there you fucking dumb cunt. What are you gonna say now, huh? That's me right there
That's right. I'm giving you the finger too
Stupid oh, oh, it's AI. Oh, okay. Okay
Now it's fucking AI
See you don't believe shit because you're a liar. That's me you dumb dumb
That's me sitting there with my mega hat
You missed bitch
No boy, oh she won't believe anything dude. She lies so much. She thinks everybody's a liar
You with the truths in their inner face, you won't fucking believe anything
I'm not here for you to fucking prove or not believe anything I say
You can either believe it or not
Believe it or not
You mean I can't believe I got rid of your picture. I must have one of you
What's this? Is this you?
Is this you or is this Jackie Chan? Hold on
Is it others your eyes I can never tell
Is that you
Your eyes are so wide there
Might be a boy actually. I might be a dude. Oh
Mr.. God
I see you
I'm sure psyche's getting like 20 emails
Well, I do anything we're having fun up here. We're having a good time. It's a party. We're having a fucking party
I'm not playing any music. I'm not showing any porn
I'm having a fucking ball
I can sense everybody down there having a great time. There must be like 80 people in the room right now
This is a picture of my dad
he caught me he caught me on youtube one he didn't he didn't look too happy when he caught me on youtube
he's like fuck again what are you doing on youtube all day get the fuck off youtube he said
i said dad listen don't worry about it have a good time remember a couple laughs
are you shut the fuck up or are your threats mean nothing to me fucking fake
threats you have no power here bitch you have no fucking power here I don't give
a fuck what you do you want me to share something with everybody you want to
keep playing with me you want to play a little girl
Play I'll play your fucking game. You want to play with me? Let's play
Let's play
Let's play a little game I like to call whose underwear is this
Shame on you, Yumi. You forced me to do this. I didn't want to do this, but you forced me to do this.
Well, before I do that, this is Yumi's father.
Mr. Justin sure, please don't laughing. Okay, Mr. Justin. He went to a secret panel and wear a mask
He a fat one. Oh
Mr. God you begging for a power
Mr. God you I will share it to mr. Justin. Oh
I will share to mr. Psycho your face with the mask. How is it? How is it?
You trigger you trigger. Oh you me you trigger. Oh, no you trigger. Yes
Yes, I trigger you I
Trigger you you me
Oh so scared so scared you me laughs like a Chun Lee from Street Fighter
She does have those thick thighs though. She can't do the helicopter kick.
Somebody call Psyche on the phone.
Time to get up and kick me off the panel.
I don't even want to be here right now. I just feel compelled to be here.
Like a higher power is telling me to be here.
Who's this?
Why you look like somebody beats you up you look so lumpy you lumpy one
No, no, no, no, no, don't use heart. Don't use those heart eyes. You look lumpy, very lumpy.
Yeah, you Chinese, see? She admitted it. Looks like a mug shot.